successuniversity.com 2009-04-17

# Success University: About Us

### STATEMENT OF PRIVACY (UNITED STATES ONLY)

Success Learning System, Inc. (dba Success University) is considerate of the privacy of our visitors and the individual sensitivities of personal information. At Success University, we believe the confidentiality and protection of customer information is one of our fundamental responsibilities. Because privacy and consumer trust are important to us, we provide this privacy statement for you to explain our policies in detail. Our goal is to protect your information.

This statement explains our privacy policies and procedures in connection with data collection and usage governing the Success Learning System, Inc. (dba Success University) web sites which include SuccessUniversity.com and SuccessEmpower.com.

This statement does not apply to our offline information practices.

Please read the entire Success University Statement of Privacy.

#### Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of Success University.

#### Our postal address is

13601 Preston Road, Suite 650 East Tower  
Dallas, Texas 75240

We can be reached by telephone at 972-578-2100.

#### Information Collected

We collect the domain name and email address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, shared with agents or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

#### Cookies

We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

#### Removal

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by either phoning us at the number above, or clicking on an unsubscribe link that may be at the bottom of any email you receive.

#### Security

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

#### Policy revisions

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If we decide to change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes to this privacy policy so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
